http://www.bfc-creations.com/privacy-policy.html

Wild Cats
Free Standing Lace (FSL)
Quilt Blocks
Quilt in the Hoop (QIH)
Windows (Tiled) Designs
Western (US)
Trades & Professions
The West (US)
0 items in cart
Subtotal:
Categories
Clearance (5)
BFC Machine Embroidery Designs (5251)
All Designs (1766)
Animal Kingdom (503)
Baby Wildlife (5)
Animals (204)
Decorative (20)
Domestic Cats (40)
Dogs (18)
Endangered Animals (4)
Horses (23)
Large Animals (19)
Small Animals (13)
Wild Cats (45)
Wolves & Bears (13)
Aquatic (42)
Fish & Shells (13)
Marine Mammals (5)
Scenes (16)
Birds (201)
Decorative Birds (19)
Eagles, Hawks & Falcons (25)
Game Birds (7)
Hummingbirds (14)
Owls (25)
Peacocks (19)
Roosters & Chickens (12)
Small Birds (29)
Tropical (15)
Water Birds (27)
Butterflies & Other Insects (43)
Butterflies (31)
Dragonflies (3)
Lady Bugs & More (5)
Reptiles & Amhibians (8)
Art Nouveau & Art Deco (40)
Artist Ching Chou Inspired Designs (27)
Artist Rise Houen Inspired Designs (4)
Artist Sally King Inspired Designs (44)
Bags (71)
Handbags (56)
Patterns (3)
Totes (12)
Blackwork (55)
Combo Sets (18)
Cultures Around the World (226)
African (12)
Australia & New Zealand (5)
Celtic (9)
Chinese (34)
Eqypt (11)
Europe (19)
India (6)
Indonesian (2)
Japanese (68)
Mexican (3)
Native American (34)
Persian (3)
Russian (5)
South African (5)
South America (1)
Turkish (4)
Decorative, Paisley & Applique (103)
Designs by Fred (484)
Fantasy (40)
Flowers & Foliage (43)
For the Kitchen (16)
Holidays (103)
Christmas (78)
Horses (13)
Japanese and Chinese (55)
Landscapes (25)
Mechanical & Sports (25)
Other Cultures (16)
People and Fashion (25)
Quilt Squares & Circles (37)
The Arts (21)
Wild Cats (37)
Free Standing Lace (FSL) (144)
Bowls (71)
Doilies taken from bowls (14)
Lace (11)
Jewelry (4)
Ornaments (17)
Sculpture (13)
Wreaths (3)
Fantasy & Whimsy (111)
Fruits, Veggies & Herbs (31)
Fruit (18)
Vegetables (12)
Holidays & Special Occasions (295)
Christmas (196)
Easter (18)
Fourth of July - Patriotic (16)
Halloween (7)
New Year's Day (2)
Thanksgiving & Autumn (28)
Valentine's Day (4)
Kitchen Decor & More (28)
Chefs & Kitchen Ware (6)
Coffee & Tea (5)
Food (7)
Wine (6)
Libraries (12)
Flora (6)
Backgrounds (5)
Mechanical (17)
Boats and Ships (3)
Cars (3)
Motorcycles (1)
Planes (4)
Trains (6)
Outer Space (3)
People & Fashion (69)
Plant and Fungi Kingdoms (246)
Assorted Flowers (109)
Decorative (45)
Bouquets (4)
Mushrooms (4)
Orchids (7)
Poppies (5)
Roses (27)
Trees and Foliage (25)
Tropical Flowers (6)
Pocket Toppers (10)
Quilting (311)
Quiltables (23)
Quilt Blocks (158)
Quilt in the Hoop (QIH) (54)
Quilt Projects (45)
Religious (26)
Sewing (12)
Stained Glass (91)
Flora & Fauna (34)
Ornaments & Suncatchers (3)
Religious (13)
Rose & Church Windows (8)
Tiffany (12)
Steampunk, Hipster & Fractal (57)
Sports & Games (8)
The Arts (15)
Travel (16)
Postcards (11)
Posters (1)
Stamps (4)
Tribal Designs (17)
Wall Hangings (313)
Art Quilts (25)
Large Embroidered Pictures (91)
Scenes (32)
Windows (Tiled) Designs (160)
Western (US) (16)
Vintage & Victorian (37)
Funsets (257)
Single Designs (3907)
All Singles (1452)
Animals & Reptiles (300)
Art Deco & Art Nouveau (23)
Rick's Gang 4 Sizes (23)
Asian (68)
Birds (139)
Butterflies and Insects (14)
Ching Chou Designs (18)
Commercial Size (4)
Cultures around the World (1)
Dogs (15)
Domestic Cats (19)
Decorative & Projects (295)
Fantasy (99)
FSL - Free Standing Lace (31)
FRED's SINGLES (46)
Fish, Marine Life & Amphibian (71)
Flowers and Foliage (351)
Kitchen-Food-Etc (20)
Hipster, Fractal and Steampunk (66)
Holidays (165)
Christmas Singles (53)
Mechanical (5)
Native American (15)
Patriotic (9)
People (73)
Quilting (357)
Quotes (5)
Rick's Gang (36)
Sally King Designs (83)
Stained Glass (38)
String Art (6)
The Arts (12)
Trades & Professions (5)
The West (US) (6)
BFC Machine Embroidery Thread (595)
1000m Cones (338)
Colors 2168 - 2297 (36)
Colors 2303 - 2465 (37)
Colors 2473 - 2695 (42)
Colors 2709 - 2899 (38)
Colors 2906 - 3117 (39)
Colors 3130 - 3321 (41)
Colors 3324 - 3531 (34)
Colors 3532 - 3727 (37)
Colors 3728 - 6413 (34)
5000m Cones (4)
Metallic (29)
1000m Cones (16)
Variegated Thread (12)
Bobbin Thread (3)
Thread Chart (1)
BFC Designs Thread Kits (208)
Embellishments (144)
Angelina (7)
Fibers (137)
By the yard (137)
Chenille (19)
Fun and Funky Fibers (7)
Long Eyelash (35)
Metallic (21)
Popcorns and Puffs (18)
Ribbon (20)
Variegated Eyelash (17)
Order on Flash Drive (1)
Free Tutorials & More (46)
Free Tutorials & Inspiration (24)
Free Designs (22)
THE BFC BLOG
Please visit our new BFC BLOG.
We have a lot of plans for our BLOG but initially I am posting photos sent to me by our great customers showing their beautiful work.
I’ve also started to add some tutorials – I have a lot of both photos and tutorials to add.
To find what you want to look at, just u
Mar
8, 2018
NEW BFC BLOG!!!!
New BFC BLOG is live!
Mar
6, 2017
Freebies while browsing
As you're browsing designs during our sale, be sure to collect the Free design on the pages!
They are on almost every set page except FUNSETS,
All news
Privacy statement
1. WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?WE DO NOT SELL YOUR INFORMATION TO ANYONE. NEVER HAVE. NEVER WILL.BFC Creations will be what’s known as the “Controller” of the personal data you provide to us.When you purchase something from our store or any other online business, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.When you browse our store(or any other online store), we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.2. CONSENTWhen you provide us with personal information to create an account, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, on your account page by using our contact us form or by contacting us at suz@BFC-Creations.com.3. DISCLOSUREWe may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.4. PAYMENTSWe use a third party payment processor(s) to process payments made to us. In connection with the processing of such payments, we do not retain any personally identifiable information or any financial information such as credit card numbers. 5. THIRD-PARTY SERVICESIn general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.LinksWhen you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.6. SECURITYTo protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.All the personal data we process is processed by our staff in the US however for the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance this information is located on servers within the US on a secure server behind a firewall. No 3rd parties have access to your personal data unless the law allows them to do so.We have a Data Protection regime in place to oversee the effective and secure processing of your personal data.CookiesHere is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.xid - unique token, sessional.recent_login - stores your username to auto-complete the sign-in form next time you visit the store. Persistent for 3 days by default (can be changed by store’s admin).viewedResources - holds a list of cached CSS files, this is used to make store’s pages loading faster. Persistent for 1 hour.rv - holds a list of products you recently viewed in the store. Does not expire.xc_np_product_#### - holds product identifiers, used to navigate within store’s catalog. Persistent for 30 minutes7. AGE OF CONSENTBy using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.8. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYWe reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.9. QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATIONIf you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Data Protection Officer at suz@BFC-Creations.com.
About our thread
Conversion Charts
About BFC
BFC .IO Group
Privacy Statement
Terms & Conditions
Shipping
Sitemap
These designs are copyrighted and are the property of Susan Makalinaw and BFC Creations.
